Hey, I heard a rumor that Ainolo was at the hotel.
ちょっと、ホテルにアイノロがいるって噂を聞きつけたらしくて、
I came to the penis.
おちんちんに来ました
I came here for a new penis.
新しいおちんちんに来たんですけど
What do you think of this dick?
どうですか、このおちんちん
Look closer.
近くで見て
near?
近く?
Not nearby.
近くない
I want you to let me push your dick.
おちんちんに押させてあげてほしいです
I'd like you to show me the divine sun from earlier.
さっきの神太陽を見せてほしいです
What should I do?
どうすればいいですか?
Please make your dick feel good.
おちんちん、いっぱい気持ちよくなってくださいって
I want to put my full spirit out here.
精神いっぱいをこっちに出したい
Come on, I'll take it out.
き そ、出すよ
Make a piramal peason in your mouth.
口なってピラマルピーソンして
Thank you very much, Ochinchin.
感謝のいいおこめてさ、おちんちん
There may be some left, so suck it up.
残ってるかもしれないから、吸い取るんだよ、
all.
全部
This is coming up, so it's going up.
これ、まいでるから、あがってます